<style>
tr, td, .sf {
	display: none;
}
body {
	background: #005aaa;
}

p {
	text-align: left;
	font: 10pt Arial;
}

h1 {
	text-align: center;
	color: #00366e;
	font: 18pt Georgia;
}

h2 {
	color: #f2d679;
	font-weight: bold;
	font: 12pt Arial;
	border-bottom: 1px solid #f2d679;
}

h3 {
	text-align: center;
	color: #0083cf;
	font: 14pt Georgia;
}

.part {
	width: 200px;
	height: 200px;
	overflow: auto;
	padding: 5px;
	margin: 10px;
	font: 8pt arial;
	background: #0083cf;
	color: #f2d679;
	display: inline-block;
}
ol {
	text-align: left;
}
ul {
	text-align: left;
}
.navbar {
	width: 100%;
	text-align: center;
	height: auto;
	background: #d9d9ff;
	margin: -5px;
}
.navi {
	display: inline-block;
	border: 2px solid #005aaa;
	background: #000080;
	color: #0083cf;
	padding: 8px 5px 8px 5px;
	margin: 5px;
}
.navi:hover {
	background: #0083cf;
	color: #000080;
	border: 2px dotted #fff;
}
a {
	text-decoration: none;
}
</style>

<center>
<div style="width: 700px; height: auto; background: #fff; padding: 20px; margin-top: 50px;" id="top"><h1>Mirage's NaNoWriMo HQ!</h1><br><br>
<div class="navbar"><a href="#prog" class="navi" style="border-radius: 20px;">PROGRESS CHART</a>
<a href="#faq" class="navi" style="border-radius: 20px;">FAQ</a>
<a href="#par" class="navi" style="border-radius: 20px;">PARTICIPANTS</a>
<a href="#word" class="navi" style="border-radius: 20px;"> WORD HELP</a>
<a href="/neomessages.phtml?type=send&recipient=deja_vu_girl" class="navi" style="border-radius: 20px;">BOOM</a>
</div>
<br><br>
<h2>WELCOME TO WEEK 3</h2>
<br>
<p>And so dawn breaks on the third week of our adventure together. Everyone is doing really great, and I'm really proud of all of you!! :D Week two is the hardest part of the month. It's when you've eaten all the frosting off the cupcake and you're left with just the cake. But week three is biting in to the cupcake to find it's filled with your favorite flavor!</p>
<p>It can also be tough as you see people (looking at myself here) rocketing toward success. Well, I'm here to tell you that the world needs YOUR NOVEL. No one else can write it! Besides, I've been struggling to write for so long that I'm still shocked when I look at my word count. Haha</p>
<p>This week, I've added a fun "game" that you can play in real life to help boost your creativity (and word count!). I've also created the pixel(s) for the event. They look just about the same, but there's a slightly more colorful version for those of us who meet our word count goals. It's not to shame anyone who doesn't make it, but to reward those who do and still allow everyone to see how awesome you all are for attempting it!</p>
<br><br><hr>
<p>	Welcome to Mirage's NaNoWriMo Headquarters! This page is here for a number of reasons, from answering your questions to keeping track of our member's word counts and progress! We are super excited to encourage each other this year.</p>
<br><hr><br>



<h3 id="prog">Progress Chart</h3><br>
<p>LAST UPDATE: 11.14.16 @ 7:30 PM NST</p>
<p>Updated semi-daily! If you would like to have your progress charted, have your updated word counts sent to Boom by 8 pm NST the night before, and it'll probably get updated.</p>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/oGJnAjv.png">
<br><hr><br>



<h3 id="faq">FAQ</h3><br>
<ol>
<li>What is NaNoWriMo??
	<ul><li>NaNoWriMo is short for National Novel Writing Month. It was founded because many people say they want to write a novel, but they never find the time. November is therefore set aside so that we can write madly, breaking through all the excuses we've given before. The goal is to write 50,000 Words in the 30 days of November!</li></ul>
</li>
<br>
<li>Do I have to write that much?
	<ul><li>No! Of course not. You can set a lower goal for yourself. It's all about getting those ideas you have floating in your head down on paper.</li></ul>
</li>
<br>
<li>Is this a required event for Mirage?
	<ul><li>Oh my, no. We know this isn't everyone's cup of tea!</li></ul>
</li>
<br>
<li>Do I have to be a member of Mirage to participate?
	<ul><li>Nope! Everyone is welcome!</li></ul>
</li>
<br>
<li>How long does the event last? What are the Prizes? Do you have a pet monkey? What is my team name?
	<ul><li>Woah! Calm down! This event is SUPER relaxed. There are no points, no prizes (except the satisfaction of doing this!) and no teams. We're here to encourage each other. I can neither confirm nor deny the monkey thing, though.</li>
<li>Well... No prizes but these dandy pixels!: <img src="http://i.imgur.com/3tlKIIH.png"><img src="http://i.imgur.com/2mTi9qU.png"></li></ul>
</li>
<br>
<li>What is a word war?
	<ul><li>A word war is a timed competition between two (or more) people. There are two types. One is time based, and the other word based. In a time based challenge, each participant writes for the allotted time, and the person who writes the most wins! The word based challenge is similar - the person to the number of words first is the winner.</li></ul>
</li>
<br>
<li>What is a sprint?
	<ul><li>Just like a running sprint, a word sprint is a quick, uninterrupted bout of writing. They are usually timed, though you can sprint to a number of words as well.</li></ul>
</li>
<br>
</ol>
<br><hr><br>



<h3 id="par">Participants</h3><br>
<p>If you would like to be listed here, please send a neomail to Boom with the name of your novel, its genre, and whatever info you want to provide. You can change it at any time!</p><br>
<div class="part">
<h2>Boom</h2><br>
The Ringmaster's Dilema<br>
35,829 Words<br><br>
Genre: <i>Adventure</i>. No summary yet, it's a mess. And it's going to be a mess. lol</div>


<div class="part">
<h2>Royal</h2><br>
Our Castle Among the Stars<br>
14,761 Words<br><br>
Genre: <i>YA Sci-Fi/Adventure/Romance</i>. Sumary TBD! c:</div>


<div class="part">
<h2>Revv</h2><br>
Photos on Your Wall<br>
20,999 Words<br><br>
Genre: <i>Romance and Drama</i>. NYC college junior drops out to start an athletic clothes business in a small town. Things take an unexpected turn one day.</div>


<div class="part">
<h2>Lady</h2><br>
We Are the Souls<br>
4,869 Words<br><br>
Genre: <i>Fanfiction</i>. DC Universe. More to come.</div>
<br><hr><br>

<h3 id="word">Helpful Things!</h3><br>

<h2>Word Prompts!</h2>
<p>Feel free to take any of these short prompts when you run out of ideas, or if you're just looking for inspiration. I've added numbers at the beginning of each line so you could use a random number generator to pick one! More will be added as the event continues - be sure to check back!</p>
①   Dragons || Bravery || Melons || Ghosts || Ace<br>
②   Bold || Games || Kaleidoscope || Banks || Ketchup<br>
③   Dog || Solitary || Gourd || Goldfish || Roses<br>
➃   Glass || Pane || Stars || Win.dow || Follower<br>
➄   Usurp || Letter || Juggle || Guilty || Bells<br>
➅   Jungle || Hologram || Falling || Ledge || Doctor<br>
➆   Halo || Farm || Philosophy || Holiday || Lion<br>
➇   Wedge || Font || Blackbird || Decade || Lollipop<br>
<br><br><hr>
<h2>The Person and Thing Game</h2>
<p><i>(brought to you from No Plot, No Problem by Chris Baty</i></p>
<p>To play, you'll need a public space, an unread newspaper, a pen, and a notebook. This works best as a two-player game, but can definitely be done solo.</p>
<p>First, close your eyes and count to fifteen. Then open your eyes and the first person you see is your Person. Write down everything you can about them before they get away. Clothes, race, hairstyle, carriage, what he or she is holding, anything and everything.</p>
<p>Second, pick up that newspaper. Close your eyes, open it to a random page, and run your finger down the page, stopping after a few seconds. The article, advert, or picture you're pointing to now has a deep connection to the Person you've "collected".</p>
<p>What's the connection? It's up to you to figure it out! And you have to work that character and their problem convincingly into the next chapter of your novel.</p>
<p>The more people you collect and and integrate, the more points you get! If you're playing with a friend, yu alternate picking out a person and their backstory, then together you set off to write, and come back together at the end of the novelling period to read each other's random character cameos.</p>
<br><br><hr>
<h2>Word Padding Tricks!</h2>
<p>Sometimes, you just get stuck. Here are some ways that you can add a few extra words to your count! (Paraphrased from <i>No Plot, No Problem!</i> by Chris Baty)</p>
<br>
<ol>
<li><b>The Stutter</b>: Afflict one of your characters with a stutter. Not only can it double their dialogue, but the supporting cast can have long, in-depth conversations about the myserious onset of the speech impediment.</li>
<li><b>Temporary Deafness</b>: Just about anything from extra earwax to loud concerts could render your character temporarily hard of hearing. This means that everything said to them has to be repeated. And repeated. And repeated.</li>
<li><b>The Dream Sequence</b>: this, along with hallucinations, can go on for as long as you'd like, be as detailed as you like, and don't have to make any sense at all!</li>
<li><b>The Citation</b>: If your character can read, they can cite. Give them a copy of <i>Beowulf</i> and a bad habit of reading poetry out loud on the commute to work, and BAM! thousands of words added to your novel! Songs, newspaper articles, and other books are also at play here. <u><i>A note from Boom: if you use this method, be sure to understand what you're citing. If you don't take it out of a finished novel you could end up owing fees and such to the original owners of the content.</i></u></li>
<li><b>The Extended Name</b>: Say your protagonist is "Jane". Every time someone calls them by their name, that's one tick on the word counter. But change the name to "Jane Marie" and suddenly you've doubled your investment. In high fantasy novels, a name like "Hudron" can, with a simple find-and-replace, become"Hudron, Son of Sankar, Prince and Overlord of Outer Cthandon".</li>
<li><b>De-hyphenate</b>: Words like "lily-livered" only count as one in most word-processing programs, and "not-quite-as-potent-as-promised fugicide" is only two. Deleting those hyphens will make your novel a grammatical nightmare, but it will get you ever nearer to that elusive 50k when you don't want to write more words.</li>
</ol>
<br><br><hr>
<h2>Neopets-Themed Word Crawl:</h2>
<p>We start our tour of Neopia in Neopia Central, in the busy market district. To get past this part of the crawl, you'll have to visit at least three different shops - one from each section - and complete their requirements. Feel free to complete more!</p>

<b>Neopia Central: </b><br>
<ul>
<li>Auction House: Place your bid by writing 500 words!</li>
<li>Neopian Bank: Earn that interest by writing 8% of your current word count.</li>
<li>Neolodge: Take it easy by writing for 5 minutes.</li>
<li>Post Office: Have your MC recieve a letter and write for 10 minutes about their reaction.</li>
<li>Pharmacy: Word war for 10 minutes</li>
</ul>
<br><br>
<b>Neopian Bazaar: </b><br>
<ul>
<li>Toy Shop: Add 600 words to your word count</li>
<li>Chocolate Factory: Write for 10 minutes</li>
<li>Gardening Supplies: Attempt a Fifty-Headed Hydra</li>
<li>Fresh Smoothies: Cool off by writing for 5 minutes</li>
<li>Fine Furniture: Write about a piece of furniture for 5 minutes</li>
</ul>
<br><br>
<b>Neopian Plaza: </b><br>
<ul>
<li>Kadoatery: Feed the Kadoatie with 500 words.</li>
<li>Wishing Well: Send your coin down the well with a 5 minute sprint</li>
<li>Hospital: Write a cool 100 words to cure what ails you</li>
<li>Welcome Center: Introduce a new character. Write for 10 minutes.</li>
<li>School Supplies: Write 50 words for every pencil within 10 feet of you.</li>
</ul>
<br><br><br>
<p>Now that you've come to the other side of Neopia Central, it's time to do even more exploring! Just off the coast is Roo Island.</p>
<p>To pass through this place, word war 3 times, 10 minutes each!</p>
<br><br><br>
<p>Going back to the mainland, make a stop at Kiko Lake. Stop by the Kiko Pop stall and roll a dice to decide what your prize is.</p>
<ul>
<li>1 or 2: 10 minute sprint</li>
<li>3 or 4: 600 words</li>
<li>5 or 6: No prize - skip this prompt!</li>
</ul>
<br><br><br>
<p>The next stop on our Neopian Tour is Brightvale, Meridell, and of course Darigan Citadel. We'll visit them all in one swoop!</p>
<p>First in Brightvale, talk to the Wise Old King. Write for 15 minutes about a piece of advice your MC has recieved.</p>
<p>Next, head over to Meridell. The Grumpy King is out to lunch, so roll your cheese wheel down the hill and do a 10 minute word war to see if you'll win the race!</p>
<p>Finally, go up to Darigan Citadel! Do a fifty-headed-hydra to escape in one piece</p>
<br><br><br>
<p>The next stop is Faerieland. Talk with at least two of the faeries before you head out!</p>
<ul>
<li>Fyora (Queen): Write 500 words</li>
<li>Jhodora (Dark): Sprint to the next even thousand</li>
<li>Aethia (Battle): Word war for 20 minutes</li>
<li>Kari (Negg): Sprint for 5 minutes</li>
<li>Taelia (Snow): Write till the end of the song you're listening to.</li>
<li>The Tooth Faerie: Write 320 words</li>
</ul>
<br><br><br>
<p>Our last stop for this crawl is in the Haunted Woods! We'll head to the carnival, that's a nice, cheery place to end.</p>
<p>Flip a coin to determine which you'll do.</p>
<i>HEADS:</i> Manage to win the games - do two 100 word sprints.<br>
<i>TAILS:</i> Oh no! Write for 30 minutes to escape the haunted carnival!

</div>
</center>